Cherie Ann U. Oliver



Oliver's Residence P-6 Gango, Ozamiz City PH Mobile: +639776499773 Ann.u.oliver@gmail.com Skype: a.n.n_oliver

OBJECTIVES

My main objective is to be able to find a job where I can utilize my skills and maximize my potential in the fields of Customer Support, Technical Support, Project Management, Underwriting, Finance, Administrative Support, and Business Services such as Recruitment. I have a total of more than 6 years of work experience and have been working from home since 2009 and overtime, I have developed into a reliable staff. Client satisfaction and career growth is what motivates me to always be at my best in everything I do.

EDUCATION

Ateneo de Cagayan - Xavier University
Bachelor of Arts, Major in Economics

La Salle University - Ozamiz

June 1996-March 2000 High School

La Salle University - Ozamiz

June1990 – March 1996 Primary School/Grade School

EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Specialist | Resume.com

November 2015 - Present

Pleygo is a Netflix-like rental service for Lego sets. I work as a Customer Service Representative, handling emails/tickets for inquiries coming from customers as well as billing/refunds/cancellation requests from customers.

Data Quality Analyst | Dataminr

February 2014 – May 2015

Monitor data feeds that comes through via twitter feed then identify and push what is eye-witness and newsworthy tweet.

Customer Service Representative | Pley (formerly Pleygo)

May 2013 - Oct 2013

Pleygo is a Netflix-like rental service for Lego sets. I work as a Customer Service Representative, handling emails/tickets for inquiries coming from customers as well as billing/refunds/cancellation requests from customers.

Underwriter | NDRG (National Debt Relief)

October 2012 - May 2013

This is also a remote position.

As an underwriter, I review debt settlement applications and the check if all required documents are submitted and if the applicant qualifies based on a set criteria.

Level 3 Customer Support | oDesk CSS (oDesk Corp - now Upwork)

February 2010 - January 2013

Upwork (formerly oDesk) is Job Marketplace where contractors and employers of small businesses meet and work together. As a contractor, you will apply to jobs posted in the website by member employers who own small businesses worldwide. The nature of the job is remote based or home-based. I am an Upwork contractor myself, I work independently as a Freelance contractor. My longest running contract is with the Customer Service team of Upwork itself. My job is to handle online chat support to those who need assistance covering their issues with the site, be it a simple inquiry to employer-contractor complaints. Due to an outstanding performance with my duties as a Level Rep, I was then promoted to Level 2 then moved to Level 3where I handle more complex issues such security issues and credit card verification. You may view my oDesk profile for reference here: https://www.odesk.com/users/~~2ee8ee7b8a157a55

Agent – Pre-Sales and Licensing | Convergys Philippines, Inc (Microsoft)

December 2007 - May 2009

I started with Consumer customer service/customer support . We provide customers with their support options and route them to the department who can help them. I was then moved to Commercial, that's Pre-Sales and Licensing, as of December 2008.

Tier 2 / Technical Support | Qualfon Philippines

July 2007 - December 2007

We cater to customer inquiries, requests as well as complaints. Since I am in a TDMA team our number 1 priority is to have all customers migrate to a newer technology and I am part of the team who create cases for phone upgrades which is much similar to customer retention. As Tier 2, we also troubleshoot the customers' cellphones in such cases when they are unable to make/receive calls or having problems with sending/receiving text messages or activating their lines.

Interviewer/Agent | Western Wats, Philippines

April 2007-June 2007

We conduct surveys through calling listed persons and ask for their opinions regarding the services they have received, anything that concerns them in their communities and others.

SKILLS

OWhat I can offer:

Technical support from VOIP to VPN setup/connections

Customer support with fluency in platforms such as Zendesk, Velaro chat client, Salesforce, Limelight CRM, Outlook and the rest of the Microsoft office system.

Virtual Assistance/Personal Assistance
Recruitment Assistance
Data Entry/Document Processing
Order Processing
Phone-based support
Blog and Social Media Management
Underwriting & other Business Services
Reseach, phone and web
Basic Accounting
Administrative Assistance